<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>


<addon id="script.tvguide.fullscreen.skin.tycoo" name="TV Guide Fullscreen - White Snow Skin" version="0.17.5" provider-name="tycoo">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
        <import addon="script.tvguide.fullscreen" version="0.0.324"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">tycoo's White Snow skin for TV Guide Fullscreen</summary>
        <description lang="en">CustomFont Setup:[CR]1. Add Muli-ExtraBold.ttf (inside zip) into your skin addon folder: /addons/'yourskinfolder'/font/ (Example: /addons/skin.aeon.nox.silvo/font/)[CR]2. Open TVGuide_Muli-ExtraBold.txt, copy and paste into font.xml inside /addons/'yourskinfolder'/1080i/font.xml[CR]3. Restart Kodi.[CR]Don't forget to calibrate your gamma :D</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=282157</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/primaeval/script.tvguide.fullscreen</source>
        <website></website>
        <email></email>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot000.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot001.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot002.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot003.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>



<addon id="script.tvguide.fullscreen.skin.kjb85" name="TV Guide Fullscreen - KJB Skin" version="0.17.6" provider-name="kjb85">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
        <import addon="script.tvguide.fullscreen" version="0.0.321"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description lang="en">KJB Skin for TV Guide Fullscreen[CR]For optimal display please change the following settings:[CR]Background/EPG Timebar Colour=green[CR]Background/EPG Text Highlight Colour=gray[CR]Appearance/Small EPG Preview Window=on[CR]Appearance/Scale Program Image=off[CR]Appearance/Show Channel Logo in EPG above Program Image=on</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=282157</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/primaeval/script.tvguide.fullscreen</source>
        <website></website>
        <email>kjb85</email>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot>screenshot1.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>screenshot2.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>screenshot3.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>



<addon id="skin.estuary.wall" version="1.9.10" name="Estuary Wall" provider-name="primaeval, original: phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin. Lavet af phil65. (Kodi's standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65 und Piers. (Kodi Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary, creado por phil65 and Piers (skin por defecto de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Estuary skin por phil65 y Piers. (El skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary on phil65:n luoma Kodin oletusulkoasu.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d'origine de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (uobičajena Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary da phil65 e Piers. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuary スキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65와 Piers가 만든 Estuary 스킨 (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay skinn av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis standard skinn)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi's standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65 i Piers. (Domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Costumul Estuary de phil65 și Piers. (Costumul implicit pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary (стандартная обложка Kodi). Авторы: phil65 and Piers.</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65 a Piers. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary-skin av phil65 och Piers. (Kodi's standard-skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodnŏ skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi'nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 和 Piers 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d'entendre i d'utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard  brugerfladen er Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen  af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmer at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Intenta ser fácil para los usuarios de Kodi de primera vez para entender y usar.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on oletusulkoasu Kodin versiosta 17.0 lähtien. Se pyrkii olemaan helppo ymmärtää ja käyttää Kodin ensikäyttäjille. </description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l'habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s'efforce d'être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l'habillage d'origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban.  Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e usare per i nuovi utenti di Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">Estuary は Kodi 17.0 およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザが初めて Kodi に触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er standard skinnet til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det forsøker å være et enkelt skinn for førstegangs brukere av Kodi til å fortså og bruke.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este costumul implicit pentru Kodi 17.0 și vesiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0.&#10;Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Pokúša sa byť pre prvotných používateľov Kodi jednoduchým na pochopenie a používanie.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standard-skin för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det försöker att vara lättförståeligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi att förstå och använda.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Confluence is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s'elimina pot causar problemes.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard  brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Desinstalarlo puede causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi, su eliminación puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu, sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l'habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l'habillage d'origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary הינה מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi, njegovim uklanjanjem može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">Estuary は Kodi のデフォルトスキンですので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er standard skinnet til Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este costumul implicit pentru Kodi, eliminarea lui poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standard skalet för Kodi, ta bort den kan orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>



<addon id="script.tvguide.fullscreen.skin.wmc" name="TV Guide Fullscreen - WMC" version="0.17.2" provider-name="DoctorEggs">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
        <import addon="script.tvguide.fullscreen" version="0.0.324"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Doctor Eggs' WMC skin for TV Guide Fullscreen</summary>
        <description lang="en"></description>
        <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=282157</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/primaeval/script.tvguide.fullscreen</source>
        <website></website>
        <email></email>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot000.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot001.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot002.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot003.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot004.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot005.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>



<addon id="script.tvguide.fullscreen.skin.blue" name="TV Guide Fullscreen - Blue Skin" version="0.17.4" provider-name="primaeval">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
        <import addon="script.tvguide.fullscreen" version="0.0.321"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description lang="en"></description>
        <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=282157</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/primaeval/script.tvguide.fullscreen</source>
        <website></website>
        <email>primaeval</email>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot>screenshot001.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>



<addon id="plugin.video.iptvsimple.addons"
version="0.0.7"
name="IPTV Addons"
provider-name="primaeval">
<requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
  <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="2.4.0"/>
  <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
  <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4"  />
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
  <provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.service" library="server.py" start="login"/>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <summary lang="en">Add addon streams to IPTV Simple Client</summary>
  <description lang="en"></description>
  <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
</extension>
</addon>



<addon id="script.module.xbmcswift2" name="xbmcswift2" provider-name="Jonathan Beluch (jbel)" version="2.4.0p2">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <language />
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>


<addon id="script.tvguide.fullscreen" name="TV Guide Fullscreen"
version="0.17.444"
provider-name="primaeval">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
        <import addon="script.module.dateutil" version="2.4.2" />
        <import addon="script.module.pil" />
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description lang="en">Possibly the most powerful TV Guide in the world. ;) Thanks for the major contributions from: iainmacleod, im85288, RayW1986, bluezed, andy, Zomboided, tycoo, kjb86, Doctor-Eggs</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Based on the original TV Guide addon by twinther, FTV Guide and Midraal's fork.</disclaimer>
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=282157</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/primaeval/script.tvguide.fullscreen</source>
        <website>https://github.com/primaeval/script.tvguide.fullscreen</website>
        <email>primaeval</email>
        <news>
        </news>
    </extension>
</addon>



<addon id="script.tvguide.fullscreen.skin.carnelian" name="TV Guide Fullscreen - Carnelian Skin" version="0.17.1" provider-name="primaeval">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
        <import addon="script.tvguide.fullscreen" version="0.0.321"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description lang="en"></description>
        <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=282157</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/primaeval/script.tvguide.fullscreen</source>
        <website></website>
        <email>primaeval</email>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot></screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>



<addon id="script.tvguide.fullscreen.skin.lapis" name="TV Guide Fullscreen - Lapis Skin" version="0.17.1" provider-name="primaeval">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
        <import addon="script.tvguide.fullscreen" version="0.0.321"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description lang="en"></description>
        <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=282157</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/primaeval/script.tvguide.fullscreen</source>
        <website></website>
        <email>primaeval</email>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot></screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>



<addon id="script.tvguide.fullscreen.skin.onyx" name="TV Guide Fullscreen - Onyx Skin" version="0.17.6" provider-name="primaeval">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
        <import addon="script.tvguide.fullscreen" version="0.0.321"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description lang="en"></description>
        <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=282157</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/primaeval/script.tvguide.fullscreen</source>
        <website></website>
        <email>primaeval</email>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot></screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>



<addon id="skin.confluence.wall" version="3.0.39" name="Confluence Wall" provider-name="primaeval">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false" effectslowdown="1.0">
		<res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Confluence Wall oortreksel deur Jezz_X. (Kodi se standaard tema)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">جلد "كونفليونس" من صنع Jezz_x. (الجلد المبدأى لبرنامج إكس بى إم سى)</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Confluence Wall skin by Jezz_X. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Confluence Wall облик от Jezz_X. (стандартния облик за Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Pell Confluence Wall, per Jezz_X. (Pell per defecte del Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Confluence Wall od Jezz_X. (výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cy_GB">Croen Confluence Wall gan Jezz_X. (Croen rhagosodedig Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Confluence Wall-tema af Jezz_X. (Kodis standardtema)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Confluence Wall Skin von Jezz_X. (Standard-Skin von Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Confluence Wall από τον Jezz_X (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="en_AU">Confluence Wall skin by Jezz_X. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Confluence Wall skin by Jezz_X.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Confluence Wall skin by Jezz_X. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Confluence Wall skin by Jezz_X. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Confluence Wall skin por Jezz_X. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Confluence Wall skin por Jezz_X. (skin por defecto)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Skin confluende por Jezz_X. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Confluence Wall rüü autorilt Jezz_X. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Confluence Wall azala Jezz_X-ek egina.</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوسته Confluence Wall تهیه شده بوسیله Jezz_X. (پوسته پیش فرض Kodi) </summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Confluence Wall-ulkoasu. Tekijä Jezz_X.</summary>
		<summary lang="fo_FO">Confluence Wall útsjónd av Jezz_X. (Kodi's vanliga útsjónd)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Confluence Wall par Jezz_X.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Confluence Wall par Jezz_X. (Habillage d'origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Confluence Wall por Jezz_Z. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">המעטפת Confluence Wall של Jezz_X. (ברירת המחדל של Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Confluence Wall presvlaka autora Jezz_X. (uobičajena Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Confluence Wall felszín. Készítő: Jezz_X (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="hy_AM">''Confluence Wall'' - տեսք՝ Jezz_X. կողմից (Kodi - հիմնական տեսք)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Confluence Wall oleh Jezz_X. (Skin bawaan Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Confluence Wall eftir Jezz_X. (Sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Confluence Wall da Jezz_X. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Confluence Wall スキン by Jezz_X. (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">Confluence Wall 스킨 Jezz_X 만듦 (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Confluence Wall teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė Jezz_X. (Kodi numatytoji teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Confluence Wall apvalks no Jeez_X. (Kodi noklusētais apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Confluence Wall skin by Jezz_X. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Penyatuan, kulit daripada Jezz_X. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="mt_MT">Dehra Confluence Wall magħmula minn Jezz_X. (Id-dehra normali ta' Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Confluence Wall-skall av Jezz_X. (Kodis standardskall)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Confluence Wall skin door Jezz_X. (Kodi's standaard skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Confluence Wall autorstwa Jezz_X</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Confluence Wall por Jezz_X. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Tema Confluence Wall por Jezz_X (tema padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Costum Confluence Wall de Jezz_X. (costum implicit pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Confluence Wall (стандартная обложка Kodi). Автор: Jezz_X.</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Confluence Wall skin od Jezz_X. (predvolený skin Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sl_SI">Preobleka Confluence Wall avtorja Jezz_X. (Privzeta preobleka za Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sq_AL">Maska Confluence Wall nga Jazz_X (maska kryesore së Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Confluence Wall маска аутора Jezz_X.</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Confluence Wall maska autora Jezz_X.</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Confluence Wall, ett skal av Jezz_X. (Kodi:s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Confluence Wall zrychtowanŏ ôd Jeez_X. (wychodnŏ skōra we Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tg_TJ">Пӯсти ҳамҷараёнӣ аз ҷониби Jezz_X. (Пӯсти пешфарзи Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">ชุดตกแต่ง Confluence Wall โดย  Jezz_X (สกินเริ่มต้นของ Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Confluence Wall dış görünümü. Jezz_X (Kodi'nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Confluence Wall (стандартна обкладинка Kodi). Автор: Jezz_X.</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Confluence Wall bởi Jezz_X. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">Jezz_X 开发的 Confluence Wall 皮肤。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">Jezz_X 製作的佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Confluence Wall is die standaard oortreksel vir Kodi 9.11 en op. Dit is 'n kombinasie van konsepte van 'n klomp gewilde oortreksels, en 'n poging om hulle goeie idees te omvat en te integreer in 'n oortreksel wat maklik behoort te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">"كونفليونس" هو الجلد المبدأى لبرنامج إكس بى إم سى اﻹصدار 9.11 وما فوق. هو خلط بين اشهر اﻷجلده الاخرى معاً ومحاوله لتبنى ودمج افكارهم للخروج بِنِتَاج يُفترض به ان يكون سهل اﻹستيعاب بمجرد النظر لمستخدمى إكس بى إم سى المبتدئين.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Confluence Wall is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Confluence Wall е стандартният облик на Kodi 9.11 и по-новите версии. Представлява смесица от концепциите на много от популярните облици. Целта е да се интегрират тези добри идеи в подходящ и удобен вид за хора, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Confluence Wall és la pell per defecte del Kodi 14.0 i superiors. És una combinació de conceptes de moltes pells populars que intenta adoptar i integrar les seves bones idees en una aparença que sigui senzilla d'entendre i utilitzar per els nous usuaris de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Confluence Wall je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 9.11 a novější. Jedná se o kombinaci konceptů z mnoha jiných populárních vzhledů, která se pokouší uchopit a integrovat jejich dobré nápady do vzhledu, který by měl být pro nového uživatele Kodi jednoduchý na pochopení a používání.</description>
		<description lang="cy_GB">Confluence Wall yw croen rhagosodedig Kodi 9.11 ac uwch. Mae'n gyfuniad o gysyniadau o nifer o grwyn poblogaidd ac mae'n ymdrechu i gyfuno eu syniadau da hwy i groen ddylai fod yn hawdd i ddefnyddiwr cyntaf Kodi ei deall a'i ddefnyddio.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Confluence Wall er standardskin'et til Kodi 9.11 og senere versioner. Det er en kombination af koncepter fra mange populære skins, og det forsøger at omfavne og integrere de gode ideer i et skin, der er let for førstegangsbrugere af Kodi at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Confluence Wall ist der Standardskin ab Kodi 14.0. Er ist eine Kombination mehrerer unterschiedlicher Skin-Konzepte und versucht dabei, die besten Ideen zu kombinieren, um einen einfachen Einstieg für neue Kodi-Nutzer zu ermöglichen.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Confluence Wall είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 14.0 και άνω. Είναι ένας συνδυασμός από πολλές δημοφιλής αμφιέσεις, και επιχειρεί να παρέχει τις καλύτερες ιδέες τους σε μία αμφίεση, το οποίο είναι εύκολο για τους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi να κατανοήσουν και να χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_AU">Confluence Wall is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Confluence Wall is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Confluence Wall is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Confluence Wall is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Confluence Wall es el skin por defecto de Kodi 14.0 y posteriores. Es una combinación de conceptos de muchos skins populares, e intenta abarcar e integrar lo mejor de ellos en un skin que sea sencillo de entender y utilizar para los nuevos usuarios de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Confluence Wall es la skin por defecto de Kodi 9.11 y posteriores. Es una combinación de conceptos de muchas skins populares, e intenta abarcar e integrar lo mejor de ellas en una skin que sea sencilla de entender y utilizar para los nuevos usuarios de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Confluence Wall es el skin por defecto para Kodi 9.11 en adelante. Es una combinación de conceptos de varias skins populares, e intenta adoptar e integrar sus buenas ideas en un skin que debería ser fá de entender y usar para quienes usen Kodi por primera vez.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Confluence Wall on Kodi vaikerüü alates versioonist 9.11. Confluence Wall on paljude populaarsete rüüde kombinatsioon, üritades omavahel siduda nende parimaid lahendusi, et saavutada esmakasutajale selget ja kergelt kasutatavat tulemust.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Confluence Wall hainbat azal ospetsutatik hartutako kontzeptuen konbinaketa da. Horietatik ideia onak hartu eta integratzen saiatzen da, Kodi lehen aldiz erabiltzen dutenentzat ulertzeko eta erabiltzeko erraza izango den azal batean.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">Confluence Wall پوسته پیش فرض Kodi در ویرایش 14 و بالاتر است. این پوسته ترکیبی از چند پوسته محبوب دیگر است و تلاش دارد بهترین ایده ها را با هم ترکیب کند، تا شروعی ساده و آسان را برای کاربران جدید Kodi امکان پذیر سازد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Confluence Wall on yhdistelmä useiden suosittujen ulkoasujen konsepteista, ja yritys omaksua ja integroida heidän hyvät ideat ulkoasuun, jonka pitäisi olla helppokäyttöinen ja -tajuinen kaikille Kodin käyttäjille.</description>
		<description lang="fo_FO">Confluence Wall er vanliga útsjóndin, sum er brúkt í Kodi síðan útg. 9.11. Hetta er ein samansjóðan av fleiri hugtøkum. Ætlanin er at útsjóndin skal lætta um móttøku og nýtslu av Kodi fyri nýggjar brúkarar.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Confluence Wall est une combinaison de concepts provenant de plusieurs habillages populaires. Il tente d'inclure et d'intégrer leurs bonnes idées en un habillage qui devrait être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Confluence Wall est l'habillage d'origine depuis Kodi 14.0. Reprenant les concepts issus de plusieurs habillages populaires, il est une tentative d'inclusion et d'intégration des meilleures idées afin de créer un habillage d'interface qui soit facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les personnes découvrant Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Confluence Wall é a pel predeterminada para Kodi 9.11 e posteriores. É unha combinación de conceptos de algunhas peles populares, e tenta abranguer e integrar  as súas mellores ideas nunha pel que sexa fácil de entender e utilizar para as usuarias que utilizan por primeira vez Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">המעטפת Confluence Wall היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi. המעטפת הינה תוצר של אימוץ מאפיינים ממעטפות פופולריות רבות תוך רצון לשלב מאפיינים אלה למעטפת פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית ע"י משתמשי Kodi חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Confluence Wall je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi 14.0 naviše. To je mješavina koncepta iz mnogih drugih popularnih presvlaka, pokušaj da se objedine njihove dobre osobine u presvlaku i da budu lagane za upotrebu i razumljive novim Kodi korisnicima.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">A Confluence Wall az alapértelmezett felszín a Kodihoz a 9.11-es verziótól kezdődően. Merít sok sok népszerű felszín elképzeléséből, megpróbálva vegyíteni a jó ötleteket úgy, hogy az könnyen kezelhető legyen a Kodival először találkozóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Confluence Wall merupakan skin bawaan untuk Kodi 9.11 dan selanjutnya. Merupakan kombinasi konsep dari beberapa skin populer, dan berusaha untuk merangkul dan menyatukan ide bagus mereka ke sebuah skin yang mudah dipakai dan dipahami oleh pengguna Kodi pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Confluence Wall er sjálfgefið útlit Kodi 14.0 og nýrra. Það er samsetning hugmynda frá mörgum vinsælum útlitum og er tilraun til að fanga og innlima þær góðu hugmyndir í útlit sem sé einfalt fyrir fyrir nýja Kodi notendur að skilja og nota</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Confluence Wall è la skin predefinita di Kodi dalla versione 14.0 in poi. È una combinazione di elementi provenienti da altre skin popolari e cerca di integrare e coinvolgere tutte le loro grandi idee in una skin facile da usare e comprendere per l'utente inesperto di Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">Confluence Wall は Kodi 9.11 およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。さまざまな人気のスキンのコンセプトを組み合わせ、ユーザが初めて Kodi に触れる際に便利に使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Confluence Wall 는 Kodi 14.0 이상을 위한 기본 스킨입니다. 많은 인기 스킨의 컨셉과 좋은 아이디어를 모아서 하나의 스킨으로 만들었으며 초보자도 사용하기 쉽습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Confluence Wall yra numatytoji teminė išvaizda pradedant Kodi 9.11 versija. Tai daugelio populiarių teminų išvaizdų derinys. Bandymas priimti ir integruoti vartotojų idėjas į teminę išvaizdą katra turėtų būti lengvai suprantama  pirmą kartą naudojantiems Kodi</description>
		<description lang="lv_LV">Confluence Wall ir Kodi 9.11 un jaunāku versiju noklusētais apvalks. Tajā apvienota daudzu populāru apvalku koncepcija un centieni pieņemt un integrēt labākās idejas, lai jaunajiem Kodi ietotājiem to būtu viegli izprast un lietot.</description>
		<description lang="mk_MK">Confluence Wall е основниот изглед на Kodi 14.0 и нагоре. Тој е комбинација на концепти од повеќе популарни изгледи, и настојува да ги обедини и истакне нивните добри идеи во еден изглед разбирлив за почетници.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Penyatuan ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 9.11 dan ke atas. Ia merupakan gabungan konsep dari pelbagai kulit terkenal, dan berusaha untuk merangkumkan dan menyepadukan idea baik kulit-kulit tersebut menjadi satu kulit yang mudah difahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna baru Kodi .</description>
		<description lang="mt_MT">Confluence Wall hija d-dehra normali ta' Kodi 14.0 il-fuq.  Hija taħlita ta' kunċetti minn ħafna dehriet popolari, u tipporva tgħaqqad u tintegra l-aqwa ideat tagħhom f'dehra li għandha tkun faċli biex jifmuha u jużawha dawk l-utenti li qed jużaw Kodi għall-ewwel darba.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Confluence Wall er standardskallet for Kodi 9.11 og oppover. Det er en kombinasjon av konseptene fra mange populære skall, og prøver å omfavne og integrere de gode idéene i et skall som bør være lett å forstå og benytte seg av for nye Kodi-brukere.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Confluence Wall is de standaard skin voor Kodi 15.0 en hoger. Het combineert de concepten van andere populaire skins, waarbij het tracht hun goede ideeën te integreren in een skin die gemakkelijk in gebruik is.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Confluence Wall jest kombinacją koncepcji  wielu popularnych skór i próbą zawarcia tego, co w nich najlepsze w skórze, która będzie łatwa do opanowania dla początkującego użytkownika.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Confluence Wall é a skin padrão do Kodi 9.11 e acima. É uma combinação de conceitos das mais populares skins, visando abraçar e integrar as boas ideias em uma skin  que seja fácil de entender e usar, destinada  aos usuários iniciantes do Kodi. </description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O tema "Confluence Wall" é o tema padrão do Kodi 14.0 e superior. É uma combinação de conceitos a partir de muitos temas populares e tenta integrar as boas ideias dos mesmos, num tema que deverá ser fácil de entender e utilizar pelos novos utilizadores do Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Confluence Wall este costumul implicit pentru Kodi 9.11 și versiunile ulterioare. Este o combinație de concepte împrumutate de la mai multe costume populare, care încearcă să îmbrățișeze și să integreze ideile lor bune într-un costum care să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit de către utilizatorii Kodi începători.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Confluence — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 9.11. Она представляет собой сочетание концепций, взятых из многих популярных обложек, в попытке интегрировать их удачные идеи в обложке, которая была бы простой для использования и понимания новыми пользователями Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Confluence Wall je predvolený pre Kodi 9.11 a vyššie. Je kombináciou konceptov z mnoho populárnych skinov a pokusom integrovať ich dobré nápady do skinu, ktorý by bol ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sl_SI">Confluence Wall je privzeta preobleka za Kodi 14.0 in novejše. Je kombinacija konceptov mnogih priljubljenih preoblek in poskuša zaobjeti in integrirati njihove dobre ideje v preobleko, ki bi bila preprosta za uporabo in razumevanje tudi novim uporabnikom.</description>
		<description lang="sq_AL">Confluence Wall është maska kryesore për Kodi 9.11 dhe verzionet më të lartë. Është nje kombinim nga shumë maska e popullarizuar dhe përpjeket për të përqafuar dhe integruar idetë më të mira në një maskë që të jetë sa më lehtë në përdorim dhe kuptim për përdoruasit duke e përdorur Kodi për herë të parë.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Confluence Wall је мешавина концепата из многих других популарних маски, и покушај да се обједине њихове добре идеје у маску која би трабала да буде лака за разумевање и употребу новим корисницима Kodi-а.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Confluence Wall je mešavina koncepata iz mnogih drugih popularnih maski, i pokušaj da se objedine njihove dobre ideje u masku koja bi trabala da bude laka za razumevanje i upotrebu novim korisnicima Kodi-a.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Confluence Wall är standardskal för Kodi 14.0 och senare. Det kombinerar koncept från många populära skal och försöker återanvända och integrera goda idéer för att skapa ett skal som är enkelt att förstå och använda för nya Kode-användare.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Confluence Wall to je wychodnŏ skōra dlŏ Kodi 14.0 i nowszych. To je miszōng kōnceptōw ze mocki popularnych skōr i prōbuje te nŏjlepsze wkludzić do skōry, kerŏ winnŏ być prostŏ we użyciu i spokopiyniu dlŏ nowych używŏczōw Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="tg_TJ">Пӯсти ҳамҷараёнӣ ҳамчун пӯсти пешфарз барои Kodi 9.11 ё версияи навтар истифода мешавад. Ин пӯст аз унсурҳои пӯстҳои машҳури дигар сохта шудааст ва ва ҳамаи фикрҳои беҳтарин дар як пӯст ҷамъ мекунад, то ки корбарони навомад тавонанд Kodi-ро ба осонӣ фаҳманд ва истифода баранд.</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Confluenceเป็นสกินเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi 9.11 หรือสูงกว่า มันเป็นส่วนผสมของแนวคิดจากสกินที่ได้รับความนิยมและพยายามที่จะยอมรับและบูรณาการส่วนที่ดีของมันเข้าไปในสกิน ซึ่งน่าจะง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodiใหม่ ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งานได้ดี</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Confluence Wall Kodi 14.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. Birçok popüler dış görünümün kavramlarını bir araya getirip ilk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Confluence Wall — це стандартна обкладинка Kodi, починаючи з версії 9.11. Концепції багатьох популярних обкладинок поєднано у спробі використати та інтегрувати їхні вдалі ідеї в обкладинці, що стала б зрозумілою та простою в застосуванні для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Confluence Wall là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 9.11 and các phiên bản trở về trước. Đây là sự kết hợp các khái niệm đến từ các giao diện khác nhau nhằm hướng người dùng đến sự đơn giản và dễ sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Confluence Wall 集合了许多流行皮肤的创意，力求把这些优点融合到一个皮肤中，使得首次使用 Kodi 的用户能更容易上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Confluence Wall 是從 Kodi 9.11 開始預設的佈景主題。它結合了許多受歡迎的佈景主題的概念，且試圖包含並整合它們的優點，使第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU General Public License version 2</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=125</forum>
		<website/>
		<email/>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.confluence.wall</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-09.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<news>Fixed home Weather item / Added 'Privacy Policy' to system info / Updated background video conditions</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

</addons>
